yourselfquotes.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | ― YourSelfQuotes.com

_We respect your privacy and committed to protecting your personal data/information by this privacy policy._  This website ie [https://www.yourselfquotes.com](https://www.yourselfquotes.com/)  (‘Site’) is the property of **‘YourSelf Quotes’** **(‘YSQ’)** (Jointly ‘we’ or ‘us’ or ‘our’) and designed for the internet visitor. This site is for educational purpose and all internet visitors (‘Visitors’) who visit this site are covered under the privacy policy. We are transparent and takes policy very seriously of user information/data.

###  **What we explain in the privacy policy**

Our privacy policy tells about **what data we take, why the data we take, and what we do** with the user data.

###  **The policy which is covered, and you will be accepting**

  *  **Purpose –** The Information collected shall only be used to provide the Visitor with the best possible services and great user experience. 
  *  **Use of Cookies –** Yes, we use it to access to your IP address. To keep a track on visitors’ choices about what they like about the website cookies and persistent cookies are being used. Knowing their past search on the site, we make sure that they do get better content every time they visit the website, visitors are informed about the new content, we try to ensure that they don’t get the same advertisements again and again on their screen, also there are a lot of filters to customize your search and to ensure that you get better results after your search. There are different keywords to get you a specific result.
  *  **Third party application and Cookies –** we obtain further information of yours like your name, email id. Our website server detects which hardware and software you are using. To know how many users have visited the website, we keep a count of visitor’s IP addresses. Through various services that allow access to our website, we gather information based on individual and aggregate search. Depending on what products and pages, the visitors have searched the most, the quality of content is improved accordingly. Likewise, we also work on improving the interface of our page for users.
  *  **Email Subscribes & Unsubscribe–** Sometimes we may ask for your email address and location to provide better services to you. On receiving an email address, we timely send promotional emails to make you better aware of our products and other details like the services we are offering to you. Depending upon your preferences of quotes like faith, hard work, hopes and much more, we periodically send you emails over a given address.  
**            **If you want to unsubscribe the promotional emails hence you don’t want to receive them, then, in this case, your case easily click on ‘unsubscribe’ option to opt out of the services. The option of ‘unsubscribe’ is given at the bottom of the page. Unsubscribing does not mean you will be prohibited from using the services of your website. You will remain as an authentic registered user of [**Yourself Quotes**](https://www.yourselfquotes.com/) and enjoy the knowledge offered to you.

  *  **Robotically data collection –** We don’t robotically generate the content on the website, rather whatever is published manually handpicked, analyzed and regularly monitored by our response team. The information collected from you by our trusted partners, market affiliates and customer service agents could be used for the purpose of marketing. We don’t share your information with any other agency who is not a trustable partner of Yourself Quotes to avoid the breach of your personal secrecy. However, any sensitive personal details like the phone number are often not shared with the third party.
  *  **Use of external link / Banner –** if you are interested in the banner ads or any external link available on our website, then we have tie-ups with other companies which you may find useful for your interest. In that case, if you visit some other website through our website, then we have reserved the right to collect your information like domain type, IP address, and information on clickstream.
  *  **Software/app/script that we use–** We use data analytics tools and technologies of the third party is being used like **Google Analytics** and **DoubleClick** Cookies to obtain your nonpersonal information.
  *  **Security Feature –** We protect user data as we have implemented verity of security feature with our site. Our site is safe & secure to access as it’s under **SSL** and running on **https** layer.
  *  **GDRP–**  European resident, we respect GDRP and have cleared all the policy here, nevertheless you want any clarification please write us mail. 

 _If You do not wish to share any information or any query: –_

You can write an email  **hello@yourselfquotes.com** to us to keep your details confidential and not allow it to be disclosed to anybody else.
